Preliminary Inventory of the Legacy of Milton and Rose Friedman's Free to Choose conference proceedings
Hoover Institution Archives
The Legacy of Milton and Rose Friedman's Free to Choose conference proceedings
2003-2004
2016C30
Hoover Institution Archives
53 DVDs (1 card file box) (0.4 linear feet)
Video recordings of proceedings of a conference sponsored by the Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas relating to contributions of Milton and Rose Friedman to free market economics.
Legacy of Milton and Rose Friedman's Free to Choose: Economic Liberalism at the Turn of the 21st Century (Conference: (2003: Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas).
Location of Original Materials
Originals housed at the Historical Library of the Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas.
Access
The collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2016.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Related Collection(s)
Milton Friedman papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Collected Works of Milton Friedman website, http://miltonfriedman.hoover.org
Collected Works of Milton Friedman Project Transcripts, Hoover Institution Archives
Free to Choose: video tape, 1980, Hoover Institution Archives
Scope and Contents note
Video recordings of proceedings of a conference sponsored by the Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas relating to contributions of Milton and Rose Friedman to free market economics.
Original disc numbering and description maintained.
Free enterprise.; Friedman, Milton, 1912-2006.; Friedman, Rose D.
- Allan Meltzer with Bob McTeer #1, 2003 October 23 (Box 1, Disc 1000-1001)
- Harvey Rosenblum with Thomas Saving, 2003 October 24 (Disc 1002-1003)
- Eric Hanushek, Paul Peterson with Mark Wynne, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1004-1005)
- Harvey Rosenblum with William Niskanen, 2003 October 24 (Disc 1006-1007)
- Francisco Gil Diaz with Bob McTeer #1, 2003 October 24 (Disc 1008)
- Francisco Gil Diaz with Bob McTeer #2, Peter Boettke and McTeer open, 2003 October 24 (Disc 1009)
- Gary Becker with Bob McTeer #1, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1010, 1012)
- Gary Becker with Bob McTeer #2, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1011)
- Airport B roll - Lou's Becker #2, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1013)
- Gregory Chow with Bob McTeer #2, Lou's Becker #3, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1014)
- Gregory Chow with Bob McTeer #1, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1015-1016)
- Gregory Chow with Bob McTeer #2, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1017)
- Francisco Gil Diaz with Bob McTeer #1, 2003 October 24 (Disc 1018)
- Francisco Gil Diaz with Bob McTeer #2, B roll lunch by Lou, 2003 October 24 (Disc 1019)
- McTeer standup DC #1, 2004 March 16 (Disc 1020)
- McTeer standup DC #2, 2004 March 16 (Disc 1021)
- B roll, Greenspan open, McTeer and Friedmans, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1022)
- B roll exterior, skyline, bank signs, people entering conference, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1023)
- Teacher IV p.u., 2003 October 24 (Disc 1024)
- McTeer and Friedmans closing, 2003 October 24 (Disc 1025)
- Q & A and teachers, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1026)
- Reception and dinner B roll #1, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1027)
- McTeer and Friedmans closing, Dena Stoop teacher IV, 2003 October 24 (Disc 1028)
- Dallas 2/5/2004 #7 T/C, 2004 February 5 (Disc 1029)
- Dallas 2/4/2004 #6 T/C, 2004 February 4 (Disc 1030)
- Dallas 2/4/2004 #5 T/C, 2004 February 4 (Disc 1031)
- Dallas 2/4/2004 #4 T/C, 2004 February 4 (Disc 1032)
- Dallas 2/4/2004 #3 T/C, 2004 February 4 (Disc 1033)
- Dallas 2/4/2004 #2 T/C, 2004 February 4 (Disc 1034)
- Dallas 2/4/2004 #1 T/C, 2004 February 4 (Disc 1035)
- Reception and dinner B roll #2, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1036)
- Lunch B roll, 2003 October 24 (Disc 1037)
- Reception and dinner B roll #1, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1038)
- Session 1 Q & A end, B roll: Friedmans/lunch, Session 2 start, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1039)
- Session 1 Eric Hanushek, Paul Peterson and Q & A, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1040)
- End of Session 1, B roll, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1041)
- Session 3 William Niskanen, Thomas Saving, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1042)
- Lunch, Francisco Gil Diaz Part 2, 2003 October 24 (Disc 1043)
- Session 4 Chow and Q & A, B roll: Friedmans, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1044)
- Session 6, Friedmans, McTeer, 2003 October 24 (Disc 1045)
- Session 3 end, Session 4 Part 1, Cowen, Boettke, Chow, time code window, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1046)
- Dinner B roll - Gary Becker (4 min. in to end of tape), 2003 October 23 (Disc 1048)
- Gary Becker conclude, Friedman reply, Chow reply, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1049)
- Presentation - James Gwartney, 2003 October 24 (Disc 1050)
  Scope and Contents note
  In pencil someone wrote: Ziwgales, Bernanke, McTeer.
- B roll, Greenspan open, McTeer and Friedmans, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1051)
- Presentation James Gwartney T/C, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1052)
- NYC Susan Lee #3, 2003 October 23 (Disc 1055)